{
    "subject": "resource/Railway_Institute",
    "predicate": "property/city",
    "object": "resource/Warsaw",
    "human_readable": "The Railway Institute is located in Warsaw.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.933077871799469,
            "question": "What is the significance of The Railway Institute in Warsaw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8989381194114685,
            "question": "Are there other railway institutes besides the one in Warsaw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8333126902580261,
            "question": "Where is The Railway Institute located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5514683127403259,
            "question": "In which country would you find The Railway Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5323866605758667,
            "question": "What type of institution is The Railway Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47890448570251465,
            "question": "What city houses The Railway Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3098798394203186,
            "question": "What might you learn at The Railway Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24516606330871582,
            "question": "Is The Railway Institute in a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22056004405021667,
            "question": "Could The Railway Institute be involved in transportation history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1559739112854004,
            "question": "Does The Railway Institute offer educational programs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Railway Institute is located in Warsaw.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4454_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could The Railway Institute be involved in transportation history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4454_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Railway Institute in a capital city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4454_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might you learn at The Railway Institute?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4454_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4454_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"The Railway Institute is located in Warsaw\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention the Railway Research Institute (or Museum) as being located in Warsaw. For example, from document 1: \"The Railway Research Institute (Instytut Kolejnictwa) in Warsaw was established in 1951...\". Similarly, from document 66: \"Our Institute is located at the Ochota Campus, 6 km from the F. Chopin Airport and about 4 km from the Warsaw Central Railway Station.\", which implies that the institute is in Warsaw."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention the \"Railway Research Institute (Instytut Kolejnictwa) in Warsaw,\" which supports that the Railway Institute is located in Warsaw."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}